Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 7 Month(s)

Notice Period: 1 Month

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electronics/Telecommunication]

Abhinash Mallick Featured

Developer seeking roles in Software Engineering, Front end Developer, Software Development, Application Support, Project Management, Graphic Designing, Quality Management, Requirement

Gathering, ReactJs, JavaScript, Bootstrap, React. Js, HTML, JSON, CSS, Git



Current Designation: Front End Developer

Current Company: AsknBld Innovation Factory

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Developer, Software Engineering, Software Development, Application Support, Project

Management, Change Management, Quality Management, Requirement

Gathering, JavaScript, Bootstrap, ¡Query, React. Js, HTML, JSON, CSS, Git, Front End

Email - id Verified: Phone Number |

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

I have a total of 3 years Experience as Software Engineer and in this Journey i have worked and hove hands on React. Javascript. Responsive layout using CSS, SASS & Bootstrap. HTMLS, GIT, GITHUB, Hosting in AWS Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator. What drives my work ethic is buliding products start from scratch that are user centered. I hope to see real impact from the work that I take on. I am looking for a medium to large sized company in India, Ideally working on design systems and/or buliding out product features while working closely with design and product management.

Work Experience

AsknBld Innovation Factory as Front End Developer

Apr 2019 to Till Date

AsknB1d is a product based IT company providing of technology products and services for key participants in financial markets, they are building products which makes alga-trading acces4ble and affordably.

From lost one yearly am working as a fronted developer In asknbld, here T m desig1ng and developing frontend from scrotch using React and JavaScript complete intergrate frontend with using HTTP request methods / axis write business logics frontend unit testing using Jest and Enzyme design UI images banners media posts using Adobe Illustrator and Adobe Photoshop.

Infinite Net Solution as Web Developer / Designer Feb 2017 to Dec 2018

Infinite Net Solution is a professional IT company providing web design, web development, web hosting and SEO solutions in Jamshedpur. It is a Software Development company focusing on Software Development and web designing projects in Jamshedpur.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Biju Patnaik University of Technology (BPUT) in 2016

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop	>=6	2020	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3	>4.0	2020	3 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
ReactJs, Javascript	>=16.0	2020	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Bengali				
Odiya				

Projects

Project Title: DSTREET GAMES Client: AsknBid Innovation Factory

Duration: Aug 2020 - Till Date Nature of Employment: Onsite / Offsite: Onsite Project Location: Bangalore

Role: Programmer Team Size: 5

Role Description: I am building complete Dstreet games frontend from scratch using ReactJs, Javascript, Bootstrap, CSS

also im using some third libraries.

Integrating frontend with HTTP requests method, JSON and AXIOS

Write business logics for applications

Project Details: Distreet games is a online fantasy gaming platform for stocks, crypto, commodity and forex market, it is a game where participants create their own imaginary portfolio and allocate virtual capital.

Project Title: Lambda (Algo trading tournament) Client: AsknBid Innovation Factory Bangalore

Nature of Employment: Duration: Dec 2019 - Jun 2020 Onsite / Offsite: Onsite Project Location: Bangalore

Team Size: 4 Role: Programmer

Role Description: Complete Frontend(web app) Develop by me using ReactJs, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap also i am responsible for integrating frontend with backend and write business logics.

Project Details: Lambda is an exclusive quant tournament for the financial markets, based on algo trading the lambda tournament is a periodic competition that awards cash prizes to the best quantiative trading algorithms written on the lambda

platform.

Project Title: AsknBid Tech Company Website Client: Asknbid Innovation Factory Bangalore

Nature of Employment: **Duration: Oct 2019 - Nov 2019** Project Location: Bangalore Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

Team Size: 2 Role: Programmer Project Details: AsknBid.tech Company website for AsknBid Innovation Factory.

Project Title: MLPro

Client: Asknbid Innovation Factory Bangalore

Nature of Employment: Duration: Jul 2019 - Sep 2019 Project Location: Bangalore Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

Role: Programmer

Project Details: Fully automated quantitative strategies for stock market using Machine Learning

Project Title: Quant Pro

Client: Asknbid Innovation factory Bangalore

Nature of Employment: Duration: Apr 2019 - Jul 2019 Project Location: Bangalore Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

Role: Programmer Team Size: 4 Role Description: Frontend develop by me using Javascript Html css and bootstrap Project Details: Quantpro is a manual quantitative strategies for stock market.

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time